Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Armenia, 3
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Armenia., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B2 (Microfiche 165)
    - Armenia., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B3 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B4 (Microfiche 202)
    - Armenia., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B5 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B6 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B7 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B8 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B9 (Microfiche 302)
    - Armenia., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B10 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B11 (Microfiche 346)
    - Armenia., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B12 (Microfiche 370)
    - Armenia., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B13 (Microfiche 395)
  - News releases, C
    - Armenia: Azerbaydzhani prisoners of war killed in execution-type shootings''., 22 April 1994; Amnesty International News Service 82/94.; (NWS 11/82/94); C1 (Microfiche 165)
    - Armenia: Death in custody heightens fears about treatment of political detainees., 25 May 1995; (EUR 54/01/95); C2 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia: Amnesty International calls for investigations into beatings of opposition supporters following election protests., 8 October 1996; (EUR 54/02/96); C3 (Microfiche 202)
    - Armenia: Amnesty International appeals against the death sentences of three political prisoners., 11 December 1996; (EUR 54/01/96); C4 (Microfiche 202)
    - Armenia: Amnesty International urges the Armenian Government to implement recommendations of the UN Human Rights Committee., 6 November 1998; (EUR 54/06/98); C5 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia: Time to work towards ending torture., 20 November 2000; (EUR 54/11/00); C6 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia: A positive step towards religious freedom., 19 September 2001; (EUR 54/08/01); C7 (Microfiche 302)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Armenia., 1 September 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter September 1993 (Focus - The shattered union: Amnesty International's concerns in the former USSR).; (NWS 21/06/93); D1 (Microfiche 148)
    - Armenia: Lack of executioners means years waiting on death row., 1 February 1994; AI Newsletter February 1994.; (NWS 21/02/94); D2 (Microfiche 165)
    - Armenia: Prisoner of conscience John Martirosyan (Worldwide Appeals)., 1 March 1998; Amnesty International Newsletter March 1998.; (NWS 21/02/98); D3 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia: John Martirosian and others., 1 March 1999; AI Works: Updates to Worldwide Appeals and news about the impact of Amnesty International. March 1999.; (NWS 22/01/99); D4 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia: Worldwide appeals: Imprisonment of conscientious objectors., 1 June 2001; The Wire, June 2001. Vol.31, No.4.; (NWS 21/05/01); D5 (Microfiche 302)
    - Armenia: Worldwide appeal updates., 1 September 2001; The Wire, September 2001. Vol. 31, No.6.; (NWS 21/07/01); D6 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Worldwide appeals updates: Your appeals make a difference., 1 February 2002; The Wire, February 2002. Vol. 32, No. 1.; (NWS 21/01/02); D7 (Microfiche 321)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Republic of Armenia: Retentionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E1 (Microfiche 132)
    - Mongolia, Albania, Armenia: death penalty statistics., 4/1992; Death Penalty News April 1992.; (ACT 53/02/92); E2 (Microfiche 132)
    - Armenia: the death penalty; conscientious objection to military service; alleged human rights violations in Nagorno-Karabakh; ratification on international human rights instruments., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E3 (Microfiche 132)
    - Armenia: the death penalty; hostage-taking., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E4 (Microfiche 132)
    - Armenia: Reduction of capital offences., 12/1992; Death Penalty News: December 1992.; (ACT 53/05/92); E5 (Microfiche 132)
    - SURAN 12/92: Republic of Armenia: Sevak Misakovich Yedigaryan, Vagarsh Agvanovich Ovanyan, Zaven Nikolaevich Sargsyan., 29/5/1992; (EUR 54/01/92); E6 (Microfiche 132)
    - Azerbaydzhan: Hostages in the Karabakh conflict: civilians continue to pay the price., 28 May 1993; (EUR 55/08/93); E7 (Microfiche 148)
    - Armenia: Hostage taking in the Karabakh conflict; the death penalty., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E8 (Microfiche 148)
    - Armenia: hostage taking; the death penalty; ratifications., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E9 (Microfiche 165)
    - Republic of Armenia: Maarif Ali ogly Aliyev., 3 May 1994; (EUR 54/02/94); E10 (Microfiche 165)
    - Armenia: Hostage-taking; the death penalty; deaths of Azerbaijani prisoners., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E11 (Microfiche 165)
    - Armenia: Allegations of ill-treatment in detention; the death penalty; deaths of Azerbaijani prisoners; hostage-taking., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E12 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia: Release of prisoners; attacks on minority religious groups; allegations of ill-treatment and fair trial concern in the Dro'' case., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E13 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia: Comments on the initial report submitted to the United Nations Committee Against Torture., 1 October 1995; (EUR 54/04/95); E14 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia: Allegations of ill-treatment - an update., 1 November 1995; (EUR 54/05/95); E15 (Microfiche 183)
    - Armenia., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E16 (Microfiche 203)
    - Armenia., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E17 (Microfiche 203)
    - Armenia: Further allegations of ill-treatment in detention., 1 October 1996; (EUR 54/03/96); E18 (Microfiche 203)
    - Armenia., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E19 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia: Time to abolish the death penalty., 1 April 1997; (EUR 54/03/97); E20 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia: The death penalty., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E21 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia., 1 September 1997; CIS: Amnesty International working against laws punishing sexual relations between men.; (EUR 04/09/97); E22 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia: Imprisonment of conscientious objectors; allegations of unfair trials of political prisoners - result of the Dro case appeal; attack on human rights library; the death penalty; prospects for repeal of legislation on homosexuality., 1 November 1997; AI Concerns in Europe:July-October 1997 Supplement.; (EUR 01/07/97); E23 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia: Prisoners of conscience John Martirosyan, Yerem Nazaretyan, Tigran Petrosyan and Samvel Manukyan., 22 December 1997; (EUR 54/04/97); E24 (Microfiche 222)
    - Armenia: Summary of Amnesty International's concerns., 1 January 1998; (EUR 54/01/98); E25 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia: Imprisonment of conscientious objectors; allegations of unfair trials as political prisoners; death in custody of Manvel Virabyan; response of the new Procurator General; the death penalty; prospects for repeal of legislation on homosexuality., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E26 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia., 1 April 1998; The death penalty worldwide: Developments in 1997.; (ACT 50/04/98); E27 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia: Comments on the initial report submitted to the United Nations Human Rights Committee., 1 September 1998; (EUR 54/05/98); E28 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia: Release of political prisoners; Presidential Human Rights Commission, and proposal for an Ombudsman's office; imprisonment of conscientious objectors; the death penalty., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E29 (Microfiche 241)
    - Armenia., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July-December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E30 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia: Imprisoned conscientious objectors., 5 May 1999; (EUR 54/02/99); E31 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia: Prisoners of conscience., 1 August 1999; Concerns in Europe January - June 1999.; (EUR 01/02/99); E32 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia: Respect my human dignity'': Imprisonment of conscientious objectors., 1 September 1999; (EUR 54/06/99); E33 (Microfiche 260)
    - Armenia., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E34 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia: Torture and ill-treatment: Comments on the second periodic report to the United Nations Committee against Torture., 1 April 2000; (EUR 54/02/00); E35 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E36 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia: Briefing for the United Nations Committee Against Torture., 1 October 2000; (EUR 54/10/00); E37 (Microfiche 281)
    - Armenia:Conclusions and recommendations of the UN Committee Against Torture., 1 February 2001; (EUR 54/01/01); E38 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E39 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Appeal case: Death in custody of Artush Ghazarian., 2 May 2001; (EUR 54/04/01); E40 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Appeal cases: Alleged beatings of journalist Vahagn Ghukasian at the Ministry of Internal Affairs., 2 May 2001; (EUR 54/05/01); E41 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Alleged ill-treatment of detainees arrested in connection with the October 1999 shootings in the Armenian parliament., 2 May 2001; (EUR 54/06/01); E42 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E43 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Allege ill-treatment of detainees arrested in connection with the October 1999 shootings in the Armenian parliament., 19 October 2001; (EUR 54/09/01); E44 (Microfiche 303)
    - Armenia: Alleged ill-treatment at the Ministry of Internal Affairs and subsequent anonymous intimidation of journalist Vahagn Ghukasian., 19 October 2001; (EUR 54/10/01); E45 (Microfiche 303)
    - Commonwealth of Independent States: Political prisoners in Azerbaijan and Armenia: Amnesty International's concerns and recommendations., 20 January 2002; (EUR 04/01/02); E46 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia: Appeal case: Alleged ill-treatment of serviceman Karen Asloian., 2 April 2002; (EUR 54/01/02); E47 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia: Appeal case: The death in custody of Artush Ghazarian., 9 April 2002; (EUR 54/02/02); E48 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia:, 28 May 2002; Good news stories for 2001.; (ORG 10/04/02); E49 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E50 (Microfiche 321)
    - Armenia:, 1 July 2003; News In Brief. In: Death Penalty News: July 2003.; (ACT 53/003/03); E51 (Microfiche 346)
    - Armenia:, 6 April 2004; The Death Penalty Worldwide: Developments in 2003.; (ACT 50/07/04); E52 (Microfiche 370)
    - Armenia: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E53 (Microfiche 370)
    - Armenia:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E54 (Microfiche 370)
    - Armenia:, 4 October 2004; Belarus and Uzbekistan: The Last Executioners: The trend towards abolition in the former Soviet space.; (EUR 04/09/04); E55 (Microfiche 370)
    - Armenia., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E56 (Microfiche 395)
- Austria, 4
  - Publications, A
    - Austria., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A1 (Microfiche 96)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Amnesty International report 1987., B1 (Microfiche 77)
    - Austria., 1988; Amnesty International report 1988 (covers January to December 1987).; B2 (Microfiche 87)
    - Austria., 1989; Amnesty International report 1989 (covers January to December 1988).; B3 (Microfiche 96)
    - Austria., 1990; Amnesty International Report 1990.; (POL 10/03/90); B4 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria., 1991; Amnesty International Report 1991.; (POL 10/01/91); B5 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria., 9/7/1992; Amnesty International Report 1992.; (POL 10/01/92); B6 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B7 (Microfiche 148)
    - Austria., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B8 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B9 (Microfiche 183)
    - Austria., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B10 (Microfiche 203)
    - Austria., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B11 (Microfiche 222)
    - Austria., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B12 (Microfiche 241)
    - Austria., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B13 (Microfiche 281)
    - Austria., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B14 (Microfiche 303)
    - Austria., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B15 (Microfiche 321)
    - Austria., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B16 (Microfiche 346)
    - Austria., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B17 (Microfiche 370)
    - Austria., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B18 (Microfiche 395)
  - News releases, C
    - Regional news item: Amnesty International cites ill-treatment of detainees by Austrian police., 9/1/1990; (EUR 13/01/90); C1 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria: Amnesty International criticizes proposed changes to Austrian legislation on conscientious objection., 28 January 1994; Amnesty International News Service 18/94.; (NWS 11/18/94); C2 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: Allegations of cruel, inhuman and degrading treatment by police and prison officers., 7 June 1994; Amnesty International News Service 106/94.; (NWS 11/106/94); C3 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: Amnesty International criticizes draft legislation on conscientious objection., 6 June 1995; (EUR 13/01/95); C4 (Microfiche 183)
    - Austria: Conscientious objector faces possible detention: Amnesty International criticizes proposed amendment to legislation., 23 October 1996; (EUR 13/05/96); C5 (Microfiche 203)
    - Austria: Conscientious objector faces possible imprisonment., 9 December 1996; (EUR 13/06/96); C6 (Microfiche 203)
    - Austria: Death of Nigerian Asylum seeker: Amnesty International expresses concern to authorities., 6 May 1999; (EUR 13/03/99); C7 (Microfiche 260)
    - Iraq: Amnesty International's position concerning possible legal proceedings against a high ranking Iraqi official in Austria., 17 August 1999; (MDE 14/07/99); C8 (Microfiche 260)
    - Austria: Incidents of police brutality continue., 24 March 2000; (EUR 13/07/00); C9 (Microfiche 281)
    - Austria: Restrictions on consensual sexual activity., 26 February 2001; (EUR 13/01/01); C10 (Microfiche 303)
    - Federal Republic of Yugoslavia (Kosovo): No impunity for the international community., 18 June 2002; (EUR 70/05/02); C11 (Microfiche 321)
    - Austria: Court delivers verdict in the case of Cheibani Wague., 9 November 2005; (EUR 13/002/2005); C12 (Microfiche 396)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Austria: torture and ill-treatment in custody., 2/1990; D1 (Microfiche 109)
    - Human rights violations in Europe: Austria., 8/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, August 1991 (Focus on Europe).; D2 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria: Safeguards fail to stop ill-treatment in custody., 1/1992; Amnesty International Newsletter January 1992.; D3 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria (Babur Partener, Mustafa Ali)., 1 February 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter February 1993 (Focus - Racism: torture and ill-treatment in Western Europe).; D4 (Microfiche 148)
    - Austria: Foreign nationals ill-treated by police and prison officers., 1 September 1994; AI Newsletter September 1994.; (NWS 21/09/94); D5 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: News in brief: Continued vigilance needed., 1 September 2001; The Wire, September 2001. Vol. 31, No.6.; (NWS 21/07/01); D6 (Microfiche 303)
    - Austria: Worldwide appeals: Mentally ill man shot dead by police., 1 December 2002; The Wire, December 2002. Vol. 32, No. 10.; (NWS 21/10/02); D7 (Microfiche 321)
    - Austria: Worldwide appeals: Death in police custody., 1 November 2003; The Wire, November 2003. Vol. 33, No. 10.; (NWS 21/010/03); D8 (Microfiche 346)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - The death penalty in Western Europe. (Extract), 15/6/1984; (EUR 01/01/84); E1 (Microfiche 48)
    - Austria., 3/1986; AI's concerns in Western Europe. August 1985 - February 1986.; (EUR 03/01/86); E2 (Microfiche 65)
    - Austria., 28/5/1986; The death penalty in Western Europe.; (EUR 03/02/86); E3 (Microfiche 65)
    - Austria., 10/1986; AI's concerns in Western Europe. March 1986 - September 1986.; (EUR 03/06/86); E4 (Microfiche 65)
    - Austria: Conscientious objection / Ill- treatment /., 4/1987; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe October 1986 - March 1987).; (EUR 03/01/87); E5 (Microfiche 77)
    - Austria., 8/1987; The death penalty in Western Europe (Revised Edition August 1987).; (EUR 03/02/87); E6 (Microfiche 77)
    - Austria: Conscientious objection / Allegations of ill-treatment of detainees in police custody / Freedom of expression /., 11/1987; Amnesty International Concerns in Western Europe (April 1987 - October 1987).; (EUR 03/03/87); E7 (Microfiche 77)
    - Austria., 6/1988; Conscientious objection to military service (POL 31/01/88) 2/1988 9 Austria: Conscientious objection / allegations of ill-treatment. In: Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, October 1987 - May 1988.; (EUR 03/01/88); E8 (Microfiche 87)
    - Austria: 1. Official public criticism of 1988 Amnesty International Report entry. 2. Alleged ill-treatment: Wilhelm Sommer; Christian Schindler. 3. Ratification of European torture convention., 4/1989; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, June 1988 - February 1989.; (EUR 03/01/89); E9 (Microfiche 96)
    - Austria: Ill-treatment of people held in police custody., 11/1989; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, March - September 1989.; (EUR 03/02/89); E10 (Microfiche 96)
    - Austria: Torture and Ill-Treatment., 1/1990; (EUR 13/01/89); E11 (Microfiche 96)
    - Austria: Austrian government response to report on torture and ill-treatment of detainees., 26/1/1990; Weekly Update Service 04/90.; (NWS 11/04/90); E12 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria: Torture and ill-treatment., 5/1990; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe October 1989 - April 1990.; (EUR 03/01/90); E13 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria., 11/1990; Western Europe: Concerns May 1990 - October 1990.; (EUR 03/02/90); E14 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria: torture and ill-treatment., 1/1990; (EUR 13/02/90); E15 (Microfiche 109)
    - Austria., 1/1991; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/91); E16 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria., 3/1991; Women in the front line.; (ACT 77/01/91); E17 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe November 1990 - April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E18 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria., 11/1991; Europe: Human rights and the need for a fair asylum policy.; (EUR 01/03/91); E19 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria: Torture and ill-treatment., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E20 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria: Amnesty International welcomes measures to combat ill-treatment by Austrian police but calls for further action., 21/11/1991; Weekly Update Service 44/91.; (NWS 11/44/91); E21 (Microfiche 118)
    - Austria: Torture and ill-treatment (update to report of January 1990)., 5/12/1991; (EUR 13/04/91); E22 (Microfiche 118-119)
    - Austria: Totally abolitionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E23 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria: Alleged torture and ill-treatment in police custody; update to the cases of Karoline O. and Helmut Lang; conscientious objection to military service., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E24 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria: Allegations of ill-treatment in police custody: the case of Werner Nosko., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E25 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria: The severe beating in March 1989 of two Austrian citizens of Egyptian origin, Mustafa Ali and another man, by police officers in Vienna., 11/12/1992; Racist torture and ill-treatment by police in Western Europe: appeal cases.; (EUR 03/01/92); E26 (Microfiche 132)
    - Austria: Helmut Hejtmanek., 1 January 1993; (EUR 13/01/93); E27 (Microfiche 148)
    - Austria: Allegations of ill-treatment in police custody; conscientious objection to military service; ratifications., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E28 (Microfiche 148)
    - Austria ratifies Second Optional Protocol., 1 June 1993; Death penalty news June 1993.; (ACT 53/02/93); E29 (Microfiche 148)
    - Austria: Alleged ill-treatment of detainees by police and prison officials (Ahmet S, Werner Hirtmayr, Rudolf Reumann)., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E30 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: The alleged ill-treatment of detainees; conscientious objection to military service., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E31 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: The alleged ill-treatment of foreigners: a summary of concerns., 7 June 1994; (EUR 13/02/94); E32 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: Alleged ill-treatment in pre-expulsion detention - the case of Naser Palushi., 13 July 1994; (EUR 13/03/94); E33 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: The alleged torture and ill-treatment of Wolfgang Purtscheller., 5 December 1994; (EUR 13/04/94); E34 (Microfiche 165)
    - Austria: The alleged ill-treatment of detainees., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E35 (Microfiche 183-184)
    - Austria: The alleged torture of Wolfgang Purtscheller; conscientious objection to military service., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E36 (Microfiche 184)
    - Austria: Alleged ill-treatment of Emad Faltas., 7 September 1995; (EUR 13/02/95); E37 (Microfiche 184)
    - Austria: The alleged ill-treatment of Sabine Geisberger., 23 February 1996; (EUR 13/01/96); E38 (Microfiche 203)
    - Austria., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E39 (Microfiche 203)
    - Austria: The alleged ill-treatment of Violetta J., 13 June 1996; (EUR 13/04/96); E40 (Microfiche 203)